import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet3: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct format to display the date as January 1",
    "options": [
      "m/d/yyyy",
      "d-mmm-yyyy",
      "mmmm d, yyyy",
      "yyyy/mm/dd"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "If you want to display the date in the format 01-Jan-24, which custom format should you use?",
    "options": [
      "mm/dd/yyyy",
      "dd-mmm-yy",
      "dd/mm/yyyy",
      "mm-dd-yyyy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "How would you display the date as 2024-07-30 in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "yyyy-mm-dd",
      "mm/dd/yyyy",
      "dd/mm/yyyy",
      "mm-dd-yyyy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Which of the following date formats will display the day of the week along with the date?",
    "options": [
      "dddd, m/d/yyyy",
      "m/d/yyyy",
      "ddd mmm dd, yyyy",
      "mmmm d, yyyy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What does the date format d-mmm represent in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "Day and full month name",
      "Day and abbreviated month name",
      "Day, month, and year",
      "Day and year"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Which custom date format would you use to display the date as 24-Jul-2024?",
    "options": [
      "dd-mmm-yy",
      "dd-mmm-yyyy",
      "mm/dd/yyyy",
      "mmmm d, yyyy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "If you enter the date 07/30/2024 in Excel and want to change its format to 30-Jul-2024, which format should you apply?",
    "options": [
      "mm/dd/yyyy",
      "dd/mm/yyyy",
      "dd-mmm-yyyy",
      "yyyy-mm-dd"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Which of the following date formats will display the month name followed by the year?",
    "options": [
      "mmmm yyyy",
      "mm/yyyy",
      "mm-yy",
      "yyyy-mmm"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "Which of the following formats would you use to display the time as 2:30 PM?",
    "options": [
      "hh",
      "h AM/PM",
      "hh:mm",
      "hh:mm AM/PM"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What is the custom format to display the date and time as 30-Jul-2024 14:30?",
    "options": [
      "dd-mmm-yyyy hh",
      "dd-mmm-yyyy h AM/PM",
      "m/d/yyyy h:mm",
      "mmmm d, yyyy h"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }
]
